troubleshooter.xyz 2019-02-24

# Privacy Policy - Troubleshooter

At Troubleshooter, we admit that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use our services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

### How we allow you to use our data?

We have our content purely written in our very OWN way and yes, we have got it protected and it’s our copyright. Articles on Troubleshooter.xyz may be carried on, to other websites, forums, or blogs provided that, you include a clear link back to the original article URL link. Eg: Source – [Troubleshooter](https://troubleshooter.xyz/).

### What data do we collect?

We may collect information like your website, email & your name when you post a comment on this blog or when you contact us. We do not share your email address with anyone its only use to contact you. Troubleshooter.xyz does not collect any information without user’s knowledge.

**We collect information to provide better service to our users. We collect information in the following ways:-**

  1. Information you give us.
  2. Information we get from your use of our services; which includes:

  * Device information
  * Log information
  * Location information
  * Unique application number
  * Local storage
  * Cookies and similar technology

### How is the data used?

We will just combine personal information collected from you at different times to provide the services you’ve requested & to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. Therefore we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Statement On Cookies

When you visit our websites we use cookies. Cookies allow us to identify the computer or device you’re using to access our websites – but it won’t affect the user’s experience.  **This website uses “persistent” cookies. Cookies help us to store a bit of website data on your device, which helps the site to load fast in successive sessions.**

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files includes your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Chrome or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on troubleshooter.xyz to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

### Use of cookies for Analytics

We use _Google Analytics_ to analyze the use of this website. _Google Analytics_ generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. _Google_ will store this information. _Google_ ‘s privacy policy is available [here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

### Advertisement

Troubleshooter.xyz uses third-party advertising solutions to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information, not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number, about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Browsing this website and using the information shared here clearly implies that you’re accepting the above-mentioned policies. Please feel free to Contact us for any questions or concerns regarding your privacy:

### DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).

This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history. DART uses “non-personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [this website](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

Contact Information  
Gautam Budh Nagar  
India  
Uttar Pradesh  
201008  

    **Last updated: 17th Nov 2016**
